(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T02:20:02.891681",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
In a kingdom far far away where all nyut-nyut lives, a sudden calamity strikes among the nyut-nyut who lives in harmony.
A pink giant monster has emerged out of nowhere and created havoc everywhere. A lot of buildings and villages were destroyed.
All nyut-nyut were left hopeless until a mysterious magical squirrel arrived to find a legendary weapon, the Nut Blade.
The legend said that this mysterious squirrel will bring an end to this calamity...
強く
To become strong...
なれる
and be able to...
理由を知った
I found a reason...
僕を
so take...
連れて
me along...
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
I feel dizzy from the muddy flashback...
こわばる心
My stiffened heart...
震える手は
...and my trembling hands
掴みたいものがある
have something they want to grab onto.
それだけさ
That's all.
夜の匂いに
In the scent of the night,
空睨んでも
even if I stare up at the sky,
変わっていけるのは
the only thing that can change
自分自身だけ
is myself.
それだけさ
That's all.
強く なれる 理由を知った
I've learned the reason to become strong.
僕を 連れて 進め
Take me along and move forward!
どうしたって!
No matter what!
消せない夢も 止まれない今も
Dreams I can't erase, and an unstoppable present...
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become stronger for someone else...
ありがとう 悲しみよ
Thank you, sadness.
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I learned the meaning of defeat.
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly, crimson lotus flower!
運命を 照らして
Shining a light on my destiny.
イナズマの雑音が耳を刺す
The noise of lightning pierces my ears.
戸惑う心
With a bewildered heart,
優しいだけじゃ守れないものがある?
is there anything I can protect just by being nice?
わかってるけど
I know that, but...
水面下で絡まる善悪
Good and evil entangle beneath the surface,
透けて見える偽善に天罰
divine punishment for hypocrisies laid bare.
(tell me why, tell me why, tell me why, tell me, I don't need you)
逸材の花より
Rather than a flower of supreme talent,
挑み続け咲いた一輪が美しい
a single blossom that keeps striving to bloom is beautiful.
乱暴に敷き詰められた
Even on this rough road
トゲだらけの道も
strewn with sharp thorns...
本気の僕だけに現れるから
...it only appears for my earnest self.
乗り越えてみせるよ
I'll show you I can overcome it!
簡単に片付けられた
Even the dreams easily brushed aside,
守れなかった夢も
the ones I couldn't protect...
紅蓮の心臓に根を生やし
...have taken root in this crimson heart
この血に宿ってる
and dwell within this blood.
人知れず儚い
A secret, fleeting...
散りゆく結末
...and scattering end.
無情に破れた
Torn apart heartlessly,
悲鳴の風吹く
a screaming wind blows.
誰かの笑う影
Someone's laughing shadow,
誰かの泣き声
someone's crying voice...
誰もが幸せを願ってる
...everyone is wishing for happiness.
どうしたって!
No matter what!
消せない夢も 止まれない今も
Dreams I can't erase, and an unstoppable present...
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become stronger for someone else...
ありがとう 悲しみよ
Thank you, sadness.
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I learned the meaning of defeat.
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly, crimson lotus flower!
運命を照らして
Shining a light on my destiny.
Oh no! Everything is burned down!
My house and the entire village is destroyed!
What is going on? Are you alright?
A giant monster burned down my entire village with its fire breath.
That is bad. Do you know where that monster is heading?
I think it's headed to the next village.
Don't worry, I shall take care of it for you so it won't destroy the other village too.
In order to do that, I need to collect power by singing and music.
So please, lend me your power, oh dear villager.
Oh, I will!
星を回せ 世界の真ん中で
Spin the stars, right in the middle of the world
くしゃみすれば どこかの森で蝶が乱舞
If I sneeze, a butterfly will dance wildly in a forest somewhere
キミが守る ドアの鍵はデタラメ
The key to the door you protect is non-existent
恥ずかしい物語
An embarrassing story
舐め合っても ライオンは強い
Even if they lick each other's wounds, the lion is strong
生き残りたい 生き残りたい
I want to survive, I want to survive
まだ生きてたくなる
It makes me want to keep living
星座の導きで 今 見つめ合った
Guided by the constellations, we locked eyes just now
生き残りたい
I want to survive
途方に暮れて キラリ枯れてゆく
At a complete loss, withering away in a sparkle
本気のカラダ 見せ付けるまで
Until I show you my true form,
私 眠らない
I won't sleep!
風は やがて 東へ向かうだろう
The wind will eventually head toward the east, right?
高気圧 この星の氷河を襲う
High pressure attacks the glaciers of this planet
さそい水を 飲んだ胸が痛い
My chest hurts from drinking the priming water
遠巻きな物語
A distant story
かじり合う 骨の奥まで
Gnawing at each other, deep to the bone
生き残りたい 生き残りたい
I want to survive, I want to survive
まだ生きてたくなる
It makes me want to keep living
星座の導きで 今 見つめ合った
Guided by the constellations, we locked eyes just now
生き残りたい
I want to survive
途方に暮れて キラリ枯れてゆく
At a complete loss, withering away in a sparkle
本気のカラダ 見せ付けるまで
Until I show you my true form,
私 眠らない
I won't sleep!
We should try to survive
何しに生まれたの？
What was I born to do?
何しにここにいる？
What am I here to do?
生き残りたい 埋まらない傷
I want to survive, my unhealed wounds...
光恐れてた
...were afraid of the light
許された命が 今 惹かれ合った
Our forgiven lives just drew close to each other
さまよい果てて 君のとなりで
After wandering endlessly, right by your side,
ほてり 鎮めたい
I want to soothe this feverish heat
本気のカラダ 見せ付けるまで
Until I show you my true form,
私 眠らない
I won't sleep!
生き残りたい がけっぷちでいい
I want to survive, even on the edge of a cliff!
君を愛してる
I love you
目覚めた命が 今 惹かれ合った
Our awakened lives just drew close to each other
狂気に代えて 祈り 捧ぐよ
Turning it into madness, I offer my prayers
君を愛してる
I love you
星座の導きで
By the guidance of the constellations...
生き残りたい まだ生きてたい
I want to survive, I still want to live!
君を愛してる
I love you
本気のココロ 見せ付けるまで
Until I show you my true heart,
私 眠らない
I won't sleep!
星が降る
Falling Stars
羽のないこの私が
Without wings, I...
憧れてたあの空
...longed for that sky.
背伸びして星を掴む
Reaching up to grab a star,
真似をしてみた
I tried to imitate it.
負けないで願いさえも
Don't lose hope, even if the wishes...
呑み込む闇 それでも
...are swallowed by darkness, still...
手探りで
Fumbling in the dark,
夢の欠片 集めに行くよ
I'll go gather the fragments of my dreams.
ただグルグル回る
Just spinning around and around,
車輪の中で
inside the wheel.
走っても走っても
No matter how much I run, how far I go,
辿り着けなくて
I can never reach you.
先を行く君の
Always walking ahead of me,
背中ばかりを見ていた
I only ever watched your back.
いつか越えられる
Someday, I'll surpass you.
もっと強くなりたい
I want to become much stronger.
たったひとり生まれてきた
Born into this world all alone,
その記憶も無くして
even losing those memories,
泣き声も届かないと
even if I lament that my crying voice
嘆いてみても
cannot reach you...
信じていい大きな木に
To the great tree that I believed in,
しがみついた爪痕
are the claw marks left behind as I clung on.
あの空へ
To that sky,
近づこうとしている証
they are proof that I am trying to reach closer.
風が雲を流して
The wind washes the clouds away...
星が降る
The stars fall.
羽のないこの私が
Without wings, I...
憧れてたあの空
...longed for that sky.
背伸びして星を掴む
Reaching up to grab a star,
真似をしてみた
I tried to imitate it.
負けないで願いさえも
Don't lose hope, even if the wishes...
呑み込む闇 それでも
...are swallowed by darkness, still...
手探りで
Fumbling in the dark,
夢の欠片 集めに行くよ
I'll go gather the fragments of my dreams.
I think after all the singing,
my power is still not enough to defeat the giant pink monster!
I heard you, young warrior.
I can help you with your worry.
...as I, the keeper of legendary weapon, Nut Blade, will lend you its power.
...as I, the keeper of the legendary weapon, Nut Blade, will lend you its power.
Is this... the voice of the Fire Blade Priestess?
Yes, you are right. I will lend you the power of this Nut Blade if you can prove yourself that you have the spirit to fight the pink giant monster.
Okay!
Dragon, One!
胸に刻めよ 時代のリーダー
Carve it into your chest, the leader of the era!
Who!
見た目よりかは かなりクレーバー
Much cleverer than they look.
Fool!
乾いた心 すさむよりは
Rather than letting your dry heart grow cold...
Fight!
時に泣いてみれば
Try crying sometimes...
見えてくる
...and you will start to see.
明日駆けるのは
Running towards tomorrow...
紛れもなく新しい自分
...is unmistakably a brand new you.
誰のためでもなく
Not for anyone else's sake,
ただもっと上を目指せ
just aim even higher!
Dragon Screamer!
Why I do? Why I do? Hoo!
昇る龍のようだ
Just like a rising dragon!
Why I do? Why I do? Hoo!
金の光が呼んだ未来が
The future called by the golden light...
導くんだ 僕らを
...will guide us forward!
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No question!
Dragon, Four!
One!
見えているのに はるかなゴールは
Though in sight, the distant goal...
Where!
見た目よりかは かなりに harder
...is much harder than it looks.
Hard!
君が踏み出す 勇気持てば
If you have the courage to take a step forward...
Fight!
やがて開く道が
目指すべき
...the path that will eventually open up...
...is the one you should aim for.
場所選ぶのは
Choosing the destination...
まぎれもなく新しい自分
...is unmistakably a brand new you.
翼を手にした
Having obtained your wings,
君は
you...
どんな山も越える
...can cross any mountain!
Dragon Screamer!
Why I say? Why I say? Hoo!
叫ぶ竜のようだ
Just like a roaring dragon!
Why I say? Why I say? Hoo!
銀の嵐が吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm will blow away...
迷いとか恐れを
...all of your doubts and fears.
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No question!
Oh my way 走り出せ! 駆け抜けてく ライバルという風
Oh my way, start running! Run past the wind called rivals.
In that case 気持ち high pace で征す 光り射す明日 まだ見ぬ上目指す
In that case, conquer with a high pace! Aiming for a shining tomorrow and unseen heights.
諦めず捜し続け finally いつまでも変わらぬ夢 victory
Keep searching without giving up, finally, an unchanging dream of victory.
空に浮かぶ dragon 背中に光り射す明日 世界をその手に
A dragon floating in the sky, a shining tomorrow at your back, take the world in your hands!
Dragon Screamer!
Why I do? Why I do? Hoo!
昇る龍のようだ
Just like a rising dragon!
Why I do? Why I do? Hoo!
金の光が呼んだ未来が
The future called by the golden light...
導くんだ 僕らを
...will guide us forward!
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No question!
Dragon Screamer!
Why I say? Why I say? Hoo!
叫ぶ竜のようだ
Just like a roaring dragon!
Why I say? Why I say? Hoo!
銀の嵐が吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm will blow away...
迷いとか恐れを
...all of your doubts and fears.
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No question!
You have proven me your spirit. I shall bestow upon you the Nut Blade.
Thank you! I shall use this weapon to defeat the monster.
Now I have the Nut Blade, I shall continue my journey to defeat the giant pink monster.
If my hunch was right, I think...
I should go through the forest next.
Oh no! What happened to you, almighty dragon?
ピンクの巨獣にやられた。今は力が入らん。
I was defeated by a pink giant beast. I have no power right now.
巣も破壊されてしまった。
My nest has also been destroyed.
Oh no, that is bad! I can help you recover if you can take me straight to the giant monster in exchange!
任せておけ。
Leave it to me.
Yes!
偶然から始まる 必然のワンシーン
A natural scene starting from a coincidence...
遠くに見えたのは 揺れる赤色
What was seen in the distance was a swaying red color.
不思議な森の奥で 見つけた黒い影と
In the depths of a mysterious forest, with the black shadow I found...
何か始まる予感、怖くて逃げ出した
A premonition of something starting, I ran away in fear.
「出会い」は 終わりに続くシナリオ
Our "encounter" is a scenario that leads to the end,
だから、わざと 遠回りをした
so, I took a detour on purpose.
会いたい、なんて 触れたい、なんて 話したい、なんて思わない
I don't think about wanting to meet, touch, or talk...
かよわい君と狡い僕が「出会う」 其れが終わりさ
The fragile you and the cunning me "encountering" each other—that is the end.
残酷だってたしなめたって 運命は変わらない
Even if I complain about how cruel it is, fate will not change.
ああ どうして、君が？ どうして、僕が？ おおかみと赤ずきん、なんだ
Ah, why you? Why me? We're the wolf and Little Red Riding Hood.
きっと君は今日も この道を訪れる
Surely you will visit this path today as well,
そして僕は今日もずっと 見守るしかできない
and all I can do today as well is watch over you.
君はあの木の先で いつも通り、隠れてる
Beyond that tree, you are hiding as usual.
私は気付かぬ振りしたまま 通り過ぎた
I passed right by, pretending not to notice.
視線は交わらない
Our gazes do not lock,
声は届かない
our voices do not reach each other.
ため息だけが 虚しく重なる
Only our sighs overlap in vain.
会えなくたって 触れなくたって 話せなくたっていいから
Even if we can't meet, touch, or talk, it's fine,
頼りない君とぎこちない僕が 其処に居るだけでいいんだ
as long as the unreliable you and the awkward me are just there.
これが恋だって言わないなら 言葉なんて、無くていい
If you won't call this love, we don't need any words.
ああ 考えたって考えたって エンディングは変わらない
Ah, no matter how much I think, the ending will not change.
会いたかったんだ 触れたかったんだ 話したかった、ほんとは
I wanted to meet you, touch you, talk to you, honestly.
かわいい君と優しい僕が 出会い、結ばれる結末
An ending where the cute you and the gentle me meet and are united...
何回だって
No matter how many times...
神様に願ったよ
I wished upon God.
でも...悲しいくらい、悲しいくらい おおかみと赤ずきん、なんだ
But... so sadly, so sadly, we are the wolf and Little Red Riding Hood.
泣いてる君を慰めたくて 伸ばした腕が、震える
Wanting to comfort you crying, my outstretched arm trembles.
愛しているよ
I love you,
抱きしめたいよ
I want to hold you.
だけど、できないんだよ...！
But I just can't...!
どう足掻いたって
No matter how I struggle,
どう願ったって
no matter how I wish,
爪も牙も消えない
my claws and fangs won't disappear.
だから、ただ待ってるよ 君の涙が止むまで、あの木の先で
So, I'm just waiting beyond that tree until your tears stop.
ずっと...
Forever...
おおーーー
Oooohhh...
Ah, here you go! If you eat this, you can recover super quick!
感謝する。よし、完全回復だ。
My thanks. Alright, fully recovered.
今すぐ怪獣のもとへ案内しよう。
Let me guide you to the monster right now.
Okay, let's go!
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly! FLY HIGH!!
汗と血と涙で...
With sweat, blood, and tears...
...光る翼で
...with shining wings
今全部全部を削ぎ落として
now shedding everything, everything,
飛べ FLY!
fly, FLY!
高く FLY!
Fly high!
最果ての未来へ
To the furthest future!
傷だらけの若鳥が
A young bird covered in wounds
空を睨んでいる
glares at the sky.
低空飛行する奴らが笑おうと
Even if those flying low laugh at us,
海の果てが見たい
we want to see the edge of the ocean.
心を無にして
With an empty mind,
向かい風に乗り 助走をつけて
ride the headwind and build up speed.
Hop, Step, Jump で
With a hop, step, and jump,
飛べ FLY!
fly, FLY!
HIGH, HIGH, HIGH!
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears,
光る翼が
our shining wings...
君をどこへだって連れていく
...will take you anywhere.
青い衝動と
With blue impulse,
本能と
instinct,
爪牙を剥き出しにして
and baring our claws and fangs,
艱難の旅路も
even through hardship's journey,
夢叶うまで
until our dreams come true,
何度だって 飛べ FLY!
no matter how many times, fly, FLY!
高く FLY!
Fly high!
最果ての未来へ
To the furthest future!
ぽつり 降り出した 雨が
The rain that started falling in drops
翼 狂わせる
drives our wings mad.
行く手には 黒い雲
Black clouds lie ahead,
今 災いの嵐の夜が来る
now, a disastrous storm night is coming.
轟く 雷鳴と
With the roaring thunder
砕ける 波を 飾りにして
and crashing waves as our ornaments,
アンコントロールで
uncontrollably,
飛べ FLY!
fly, FLY!
HIGH, HIGH, HIGH!
いつも胸の奥を
Always deep inside our chest,
焦がす炎が 道を照らし出すと
the burning flame illuminates the path,
灯台になる 夜明け前の
becoming a lighthouse before the dawn.
光芒が
The shaft of light...
才能の花 咲かすから
...will make the flower of talent bloom.
命 尽きるまで
Until our lives end,
限界を越え 最高速で 飛べ FLY!
surpass the limit, at maximum speed, fly, FLY!
飛べ FLY! HIGH!
Fly, FLY! HIGH!
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears,
光る翼が
our shining wings...
君をどこへだって連れていく
...will take you anywhere.
青い衝動と
With blue impulse,
本能と
instinct,
爪牙を剥き出しにして
and baring our claws and fangs...
Yeah!
全部全部を削ぎ落として
shedding everything, everything,
飛べ FLY!
fly, FLY!
HIGH, HIGH!
いつも胸の奥を
Always deep inside our chest,
焦がす炎が 道を照らし出すと
the burning flame illuminates the path,
灯台になる 夜明け前の
becoming a lighthouse before the dawn.
光芒が
The shaft of light...
才能の花 咲かすから
...will make the flower of talent bloom.
命 尽きるまで
Until our lives end,
限界を越え 最高速で 飛べ FLY!
surpass the limit, at maximum speed, fly, FLY!
高く FLY!
Fly high!
最果ての未来へ
To the furthest future!
It's over now, evil monster!
I have the high ground!
If I love you, would you love me too?
would you love me too
utara ku kecil dahulu
My northern star when I was young
the love will last it will
selamanya 'ku kan peduli, right?
Forever I will care, right?
To me, broken thing have I become
To me, a broken thing have I become
And you see, life is pain (love is paradise)
Truly I had enough (I just never had enough)
Ordinary day it seems, the clouds of love
An ordinary day, it seems, the clouds of love
(ordinary) in the sky
painted colors in my (never meant for me) paradise
titik hujan menyegarkan (membasahi) segala
Raindrops refresh (drench) everything,
bunga-bunga emosi manusia (luka-luka emosi manusia)
the flowers of human emotion (the wounds of human emotion)
mekar dan berkembang (terlelap) megah selamanya
blooming and growing (asleep) majestically forever.
will I love you like you love me too
utara mu lebih dahulu
Your northern star came first
the love will last it will
selamanya 'ku kan ada di sini
Forever I will be here
To me, enchanting have I become
And you see life is fair (love is a façade)
truly I am enough (I will never am enough)
Truly, I am enough (I will never be enough)
ordinary day it seems
An ordinary day, it seems
the cloud of lies (ordinary) in the sky
painted color in my (never meant for me) paradise
titik hujan menghapuskan (membasahi) segala
Raindrops erase (drench) everything,
luka, duka emosi manusia (bunga-bunga emosi manusia)
the wounds and grief of human emotion (the flowers of human emotion)
rapuh dan terjatuh (bermegah), lelah di dunia
fragile and falling (boastful), tired of the world.
the halo (hollow) lingers on my ego (ego)
blinding light that radiates (only light within me)
evaporates the sad in me (evaporate, leaving me)
a soundless whisper
follow me (don't follow me), never let go
bahagia (bahagia) jadi nyata (harapnya menjadi hal nyata)
Happiness (happiness) becomes real (hoping it becomes real)
berdua (ah)
together.
To me, obsessive have I become
And you see life is fair (love is a façade)
never I had enough (I will never give enough)
ordinary I will be
the cloud and the color (ordinary) of rainbow
start to show in my (was it meant for me) paradise
titik hujan meleburkan (membasahi) segala
Raindrops dissolve (drench) everything,
luka, duka emosi manusia (bunga-bunga emosi manusia)
the wounds and grief of human emotion (the flowers of human emotion)
rapuh dan terlalu (merekah) lelah di dunia
fragile and too (blooming) tired of the world.
hi, finally I can see you (nice to meet you)
awan gelap yang membentuk aku (membawa ku)
The dark clouds that shaped me (bringing me),
titik hujan membasuh (bersih)
raindrops wash away (clean)
bunga-bunga perasaan (suka dan duka perasaan)
the flowers of feelings (joy and sorrow of feelings)
dan melebur (menjadi) satu warna yang bermakna
and dissolve (becoming) one meaningful color.
Stop right there!
I'm here to stop you and release all the Nut Nut from misery!
Wow, I can't believe
that we've defeated the giant monster!
It's actually this cute! Aw!
As a celebration, let's sing one more song!
ひらひら 葉落ち月
Fluttering, the month of falling leaves...
夜明けが見たいって
Wishing to see the dawn,
叫んだ空
the sky cried out.
ヒバリ
Lark
神様気取りのマダム達が
The madams playing God...
世界をA.I.して壊しました
...ruined the world with their "A.I." love.
ダレノモノ ダレノモノ ワレノモノ
Whose is it? Whose is it? It's mine!
邪魔ものは排除した
All obstacles have been eliminated.
カントがなんとか言ってたって
No matter what Kant might have said,
egoに掴まれて拒めないんだ
we are gripped by ego and cannot refuse.
マダタリナイ モノタリナイ シニタクナイ
Not enough! Still not enough! I don't want to die!
機械仕掛けの
Inside this mechanical clockwork...
狂った声で大人達が言う
The adults shout with crazed voices,
we doin' holy war for luv
うんざりだよ
I am so sick of this.
syndrome：アイシテル
Syndrome: "I love you."
あぁ もう やめてよ
Ah, please just stop it.
心ってモノを量って切って
If you weigh, cut, and sell
売れば幸せですか？
the thing called a heart, are you happy?
造られた憧憬
A manufactured aspiration...
もう抜け出したい 欺瞞世界 虚空の果て
I want to escape this deceptive world at the edge of the void.
魂を一体どこに隠した？
Where on earth did you hide my soul?
神よ、科学よ、イブよ
Oh God, oh science, oh Eve...
天つ少女 詩と舞う
The heavenly maiden dances with poetry
ヒバリの天
under the lark's sky.
輪廻転生 機械論 進化の論
Samsara, mechanism, theory of evolution...
人が人でなく堕ち無くなる地の片隅よ恐れろと
In the corner of this land where humans cease to be human, tremble in fear!
歌だけは未来へ届くよう
Hoping only this song will reach the future,
天から空へと繋げるよう
connecting heaven to the sky.
限りなく鳴く光
An endlessly chirping light,
ヒバリ達を遺す
leaving the larks behind.
なんて絵本を聞かせてくれたっけ
Was that the picture book you read to me?
ねぇ リリアン
Hey, Lillian...
「2人のこと愛してる」
"I love you both..."
嘘でもいいから一度だけでも聞かせてよ！
Even if it's a lie, let me hear it just once!
常世ってトコで笑ってますか？
Are you smiling in that eternal land?
今は幸せですか？
Are you happy now?
オキザリのまま
Left all alone...
届かない想い「ごめん」なんて言えなかったかな
with unreachable feelings, why couldn't I say "I'm sorry"?
悲しい思い出は風に隠した
I hid my sad memories in the wind.
歌よ、あなたのもとへ
Oh song, fly to where you are.
天つ少女 時を舞う
The heavenly maiden dances through time
ヒバリの天
under the lark's sky.
ひとりでも笑って生きるんだ
I will live on smiling, even if I'm alone.
ひとりでは生きていけないんだ
Yet, I cannot live completely alone.
ずっと拒んだり愛したり
Always rejecting, always loving...
恨んで壊して それでも繕って生きるよ
Resenting, destroying, yet mending and living on.
心ってモノを量って切って
If you weigh, cut, and sell
売れば幸せですか？
the thing called a heart, are you happy?
造られたshowcase
Inside this manufactured showcase...
もう逃げ出せない 期待 未来 奇跡の鍵
we can no longer escape our expectations, the future, and the key of miracles.
魂を一体どこに隠した？
Where on earth did you hide my soul?
神よ、科学よ、イブよ
Oh God, oh science, oh Eve...
天つ少女 詩と舞う
The heavenly maiden dances with poetry.
夜明けを告げたらいこう
Once dawn is announced, let's go
姫雛鳥の天
under the sky of the little princess bird.
うーー はーー！
Oooh, haa!
Hi everyone!
Woo!
Now, now, now... how was my performance?
Do you like it?
Did you guys have fun?
And also, for celebrating my victory
And also, to celebrate my victory
and my birthday,
we have special merch!
Yes, so here is the merch!
Woo!
Whoa! How cool is it?
And it's not only cool,
this year's merch was designed to be useful too.
So let's have a closer look, shall we?
First up...
Ooh...
Whoa!
It's an awesome A3 tapestry drawn by Netural-sensei!
Whoa, the whole illustration just...
whoa, it looks super awesome. It looks so cool.
You can see that I'm holding my beloved...
Just look at that warrior resolve
with full dark side. Isn't that awesome?
Woo! Don't miss it.
And also, don't forget you guys gotta buy at least five, okay?
And I think let's see what we have next!
Woo!
A super cute tumbler for everybody
so you guys won't forget to hydrate.
Um, you can use it to drink water,
and you can use it pretty much always.
So be sure to use it every day, okay?
And next, we have this!
Whoa!
A smartphone ring?
Ooh, so you can be super comfortable and remember me
when you're holding your phone.
And it also will secure your phone in your hand.
Very, very convenient.
And I think let's see the full set now!
Woo! Whoa, there's so much stuff, actually.
And also, don't forget we have the full set purchase bonus
here!
So I will explain it a little bit.
For those of you who purchase the full set,
will also receive a signed foil-stamp postcard.
you will also receive a signed foil-stamped postcard.
And for my super Risuners who purchase
the limited edition full set, will receive a postcard
the limited edition full set, you will receive a postcard
autographed by none other than me!
Autographed by me, isn't it awesome? Whoa!
And the pre-order window is only a month,
so make sure that you don't miss it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Also, one more thing.
Did you guys listen to my new original song, Hoshi ga Furu?
It will be officially released after this stream
at midnight JST. JST, okay? On my YouTube channel.
So go listen to it!
And, who knows, maybe later we will have MV for it?
And who knows, maybe later we will have an MV for it?
I don't know!
And last but not least,
for all of you who joined my membership,
you don't want to miss a special additional
3D performance in membership just right after this show has ended.
If you haven't joined my membership yet,
do not hesitate because the extra show is going to be mind-boggling.
What are you waiting for? Join membership
now!
Woo!
Oops, um, but I think the time is up, aww...
And I have to continue...
but yes, I have to continue with the membership show now!
So thank you so much everyone for your support
for this whole six years especially.
And thank you for celebrating my birthday
together with me!
So...
Puru puru otsu risu!
Puru puru, otsurisu!
The Rise of the Nut Warrior